(Sheldon:)oh, and last, but not least,
teenagers with guitars.
(Penny:)I'll see
if it's available.
(Amy:)You know,
if that study's real,
(Amy:)Leonard might come back
smarter than you.
(Sheldon:)Are you trying to manipulate me?
Yes.
(Sheldon:)Well done, it worked,
we're going.
Yay!
(bags rustling)
BERNADETTE: Come on, Raj,
(Bernadette:)give me a bag.
(Raj:)No, no, you're pregnant.
(Raj:)The only thing you carry
(Raj:)is our hope
for a better tomorrow.
(Howard:)Hey, where you been?
(Bernadette:)Uh, Raj took me
to the baby doctor
(Bernadette:)and then we swung by
the grocery store.
(tires screeching on game)
Did you get graham crackers?
I mean, are... what...
is the baby okay?
(Bernadette:)Yes and yes.
(sighs)
(Howard:)I didn't know you needed help
running errands today.
(Howard:)I didn't,
but Raj volunteered.
(Howard:)Really?
(Bernadette:)Yeah, ever since you told him
I was pregnant,
(Bernadette:)he's really been making
a fuss over me.
(Howard:)Oh. Well, I guess
that's kind of sweet.
(Raj:)Bernie, I just
forwarded you a list
(Raj:)of the top five lactation
consultants in Los Angeles.